# **DILUAN** LIMA DE MATOS

5TH YEAR - SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

### **EDUCATION**

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Universidade Estadual de Ponta Grossa 2021-

### AGRICULTURAL TECHNICIAN

Colégio Agrícola Augusto Ribas 2017-2019

- Number (mobile) +55 (42) 9 8404-9847
- Email

  diluan135@gmail.com
- in Linkdin
  linkedin.com/in/diluan-matos
- GitHub

  github.com/diluan135
- Portfolio

  diluan135.github.io/portfolio/

### **ABOUT ME**

I currently work as a fullstack developer, using my experience as a graphic designer to create intuitive and efficient interfaces, always prioritizing the user experience and maintaining an elegant and functional design.

I have solid experience having carried out some projects using PHP, Laravel, VueJS, HTML, CSS and Bootstrap, as well as advanced knowledge in design tools such as Photoshop and Illustrator. I seek to integrate my programming and design skills to develop complete, high-quality solutions, aligned with the needs of each project.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2021-2022 IMAGE OPERATOR

Foto Carlos

In charge of customer service, editing and printing of photographs and creation and assembly of photo products.

2022-2023 GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Agência yard.

Responsible for creating the visual and/or audiovisual part of organic posts, advertisements, posters, landing pages, etc.

2023-atual FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Transport Department - Ponta Grossa City Hall

In charge of administration and updating of legacy systems, responsible for creating projects covering front-end, back-end, data management and database creation.

#### SKILL WITH LANGUAGES AND TOOLS

VueJs	Laravel
Python	РНР
Flutter	Bootstrap
Adobe photoshop	Adobe Illustrator